{
    "questions":[
        {
            "questionId":"1",
            "questionText":"Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"Bytecode is executed by JVM"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"The applet makes the Java code secure and portable"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"Use of exception handling"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"Dynamic binding between objects"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"a",
            "isHidden":false

        },
        {
            "questionId":"2",
            "questionText":"Which of the following is not a Java features?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"Dynamic"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"Architecture Neutral"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"Use of pointers"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"Object-oriented"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"c",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"3",
            "questionText":"What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"Object"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"int"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"log"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"void"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"b",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"4",
            "questionText":"What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"0"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"NaN"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"Infinity"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"Run time exception."
                }
            ],
            "answer":"c",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"5",
            "questionText":"Which of the following tool is used to generate API documentation in HTML format from doc comments in source code?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"javap tool"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"javaw command"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"Javadoc tool"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"javah command"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"c",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"6",
            "questionText":"Which package contains the Random class?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"java.util package"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"java.lang package"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"java.io package"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"java.awt package"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"a",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"7",
            "questionText":"What do you mean by nameless objects?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"An object created by using the new keyword."
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"An object of a superclass created in the subclass."
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"An object without having any name but having a reference."
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"An object that has no reference."
                }
            ],
            "answer":"d",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"8",
            "questionText":"Which of the following is an immediate subclass of the Panel class?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"Applet class"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"Window class"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"Frame class"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"Dialog class"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"a",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"9",
            "questionText":"Which of the following is a marker interface?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"Runnable interface"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"Remote interface"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"Readable interface"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"Result interface"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"b",
            "isHidden":true

        },
        {
            "questionId":"10",
            "questionText":"Which keyword is used for accessing the features of a package?",
            "option":[
                {
                    "optionValue":"a",
                    "optionText":"package"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"b",
                    "optionText":"import"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"c",
                    "optionText":"export"
                },
                {
                    "optionValue":"d",
                    "optionText":"extends"
                }
            ],
            "answer":"b",
            "isHidden":true

        }
        
        
    

    ]
}